

CHAUHAN

Backend Developer

About Me

I bring over two years of extensive experience in PHP Laravel and six months of Java servlets/JSP proficiency, with a strong focus on crafting resilient back-end solutions.



+91 93134 40532



jay.chauhan3042@gmail.com



1 Global Residency, Surat, Gujarat, India - 395009

LANGUAGE

- English
- Hindi
- Gujarati

EXPERTISE

- Project Management Skills
- Java (JSP / Servlets)
- Php (core PHP / Laravel)
- jQuery
- Vue.js / React.js
- Node.js

EXPERIENCE

Omeecron Solutions

Surat - India

2022 - 2023

Crafting highly proficient and scalable back-end solutions by leveraging the power of the Laravel framework in conjunction with the Vue.js frontend framework.

Senza Solutions

Surat - India

2020 - 2022

Gained invaluable experience in developing robust backend solutions using the PHP.

Freelance

remote - India

2020 - Present

Entailed developing robust backends using top-tier frameworks such as PHP, Laravel, Node.js, JSP, and ASP.NET.

EDUCATION

Uka Tarsadia University

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology 2020 - 2023

The Radiant International School

H.S.C. (12th Science [PCM])

SKILLS SUMMARY

Node.js

78 %

PHP

